SRIJANA RAI

OBJECTIVES

Dedicated and results-driven Customer Service Representative with 7 years of experience in delivering exceptional customer support and satisfaction. Seeking to utilize my strong communication skills and problem-solving abilities to contribute positively to the customer service, while continuing to enhance my professional growth and contribute to the company's success.

PERSONAL DETAILS

Contact: +91 8073176347

Date of Birth: 5th Feb, 1991

Email: jann_804@outlook.com

Address: 33 Balaji Gardens Layout,
Gottigere, B.G Road, Blr - 560083

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF COMMERCE (BCA)

KSOU - Mysore University 2012 - 2015 60 percentage

LANGUAGES

English 100%
Hindi 100%
Kannada 85%

SKILLS

- Strong communication and interpersonal skills.
- Proficient in using tools, dispute resolution software, and KYC systems.
- Detail-oriented with a high level of accuracy in data management.
- Understanding of AML and KYC regulations and their implications.
- Ability to handle sensitive information with discretion.
- Adaptable and able to multitask in a fast-paced environment.

TOOLS



WORK EXPERIENCE

PayPal India Private Limited

Customer Solution Specialist | Apr 2019 - Jul 2022

- Assisting customers with a wide range of inquiries, such as account logins, deleting duplicate accounts, guest logins, purchases and checkouts via chat, email and call.
- Assisting customers with payment cancellations, order cancellations, completing transactions, cancelling pendingwithdrawals, approving withdrawals and sending cash-achecks.
- Providing prompt support with regards to order tracking, merchant contacts and payment protections (Goods & Services). Also, includes buyer's and seller's protection policies.
- Providing technical assistance and troubleshooting for customers experiencing problems such as account login issues, region change, language update, reset profiles, wallet issues, account balance issues, either resolving issues directly or escalating them to specialized technical support teams.
- Identifying opportunities to recommend additional products like, PayPal.ME, PayPal loan, PayPal credits or services like, PayPal pay-later and currency exchanges, to customers based on their needs and preferences, contributing to increase sales and revenue.
- Filing and resolving tickets/cases related to personal and business transactions, suspicious transactions/activities, goods/service purchases, billing errors in a timely manner. Working on internal and external disputes and chargebacks with card providers.
- Communicating with customers to gather additional documents with regards to the account limitations, and following KYC/AML process and policies to lift the limitation. Documenting the research performed on the accounts.
- Investigating thoroughly on KYC aspects, which includes, transaction monitoring, AML policies, sanctions list and escalating the accounts for further investigation (level II) to compliance team.

Concentrix India Private Limited

Customer Solution Rep. - Operations | Jan 2016 - April 2019

- Generating credit notes and sales order in SAP. Approving, cancelling and closing repair jobs for all Apple products. Renewing POP and extending product's warranty. Including acknowledging consignments and assigning loaner devices.
- Addressing inquiries related to troubleshooting, Apple repair programs, billing, and general product information, including product features, warranties, and technical specifications.
- Performed as QA to audit chats and emails for 3 months as a part of leap program and explored the chat reviewing tools.
- Attending con-calls with regards to the process updates and the products and sharing ideas and solutions for effortless customer experience.